imreportcard.com 2013-06-27

# IM Report Card Privacy Policy

IMReportCard.com Privacy Policy

We take your privacy very seriously, and we've created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to online privacy. This page outlines our information gathering and dissemination practices, and our use of personally identifiable information.

**What information does IMReportCard.com collect from visitors?**

IMReportCard.com collects information from our visitors and users of our website and uses the information for marketing and administration purposes, in the fulfillment of our service commitment to you, or as required under the law.

As a user of this website, IMReportCard.com may collect your personally identifiable information when you visit our site and create a IMReportCard.com account.

The personally identifiable information we collect is limited to your name and email.

**Why is information collected?**

Information may be collected in an effort to enhance your user experience, provide you with information regarding IMReportCard.com services or other related special offers, and/or to provide you with the products and/or services that you request.

We, or our authorized third-party affiliates, may also collect general information about transactions as they correspond to our advertisements or products. This aggregate information may include demographic and usage information, but does not include personally identifiable information.

This information is used in an aggregated manner to determine advertising effectiveness and is sometimes shared with our advertising partners for the same limited purpose.

**How does IMReportCard.com protect my information?**

We have implemented a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personally identifiable information. Users' personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by certain key employees.

We do not collect or store any credit card or other financial information.

Should it be necessary to transmit your personally identifiable information to a reputable third party vendor to fulfill our service commitment to you, IMReportCard.com will require all recipients of such information to maintain the information as confidential information, use the information for the limited and intended purpose and agree not to disclose such information.

**Will IMReportCard.com disclose the information it collects to others?**

IMReportCard.com does not rent, sell or share any of the information collected by this site with unrelated 3rd-parties, except to provide the products or services you've purchased or requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action in conjunction with illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of IMReportCard.com's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law;
  * We are required by law to provide the IRS with Tax ID numbers and/or other personally identifiable information about Affiliates and Writers who receive over $600 in payments from IMReportCard.com in a calender year.  

**Does IMReportCard.com use "cookies" or pixel "tags"?**

Cookies are bits of electronic information that a website can transfer to a visitor's hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. Cookies allow website operators to better customize a site to your individual preferences.

The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and most major websites use them. We may use cookies to help provide you with a better experience on our site; however, we do not store personally identifying information in cookies.

Like most websites, IMReportCard.com may also use pixel tags, also known as beacons, spotlight tags or web bugs, to improve our understanding of site traffic, visitor behavior, and response to promotional campaigns, as a supplement to our server logs and other methods of traffic and response measurement.

We may also use pixels provided by 3rd-parties, and limit the collection of information for the same purpose. We do not store personally identifying information in pixels.

**Can I access or modify the Personal Identifying Information collected?**

You can view and/or modify the information provided to us at any time by logging in to your account, and clicking the "Account Info" link. You may also submit your request to modify your account information via any of the methods below.

**What if I want to Opt-Out of email communications from IMReportCard.com?**

IMReportCard.com provides every user with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future promotional communications from us. You may do so in the following ways:

1\. Email: [support@imreportcard.com](mailto:support@imreportcard.com)  
  
2\. Website: http://www.imreportcard.com/contact.cgi  
  
3\. Postal Mail: IM Report Card.com, LLC, 3210 East Chinden Blvd. #115, Eagle, ID 83616

Please note that even if you opt-out, you may still receive important announcements or updates regarding your IMReportCard.com account unless you cancel your account.

**Can children or minors use IMReportCard.com?**

IMReportCard.com does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from or about anyone under the age of 16. If we discover we have received such information in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately.

If you believe IMReportCard.com has any information from or about anyone under the age of 16, please contact us. If you are under 16, you may use IMReportCard.com only under the supervision of a parent or guardian.

**Links to Other Sites**

This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that IMReportCard.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

**Your consent**

By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of the information you provide per this Privacy Policy. We also reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy. Should this be necessary, we will post any changes here so you're always aware of the information we collect and how we use it.

**Contacting IMReportCard.com**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us via one of the methods above.

**This Privacy Policy was last updated May 8th, 2009.**
